# **Andrew Philip Schoenbauer**

Grand Forks, ND 58201 United States 952-212-9477 andrewschoenbauer12@gmail.com

## **Professional Summary**

Hardworking and reliable student and employee, with five years of experience in the food industry and almost a year in the retail industry. Personable and experienced at handling all kinds of situations that arise with customers. Great at handling high stress situations and multitasking. Excel at developing customer relations and rapport.

#### **Skills**

- Customer service
- Payment processing
- Customer relations
- Drawer balancing
- Manage customer accounts

- Safe food handling procedures
- Suggestive selling
- Cash Handling
- Microsoft Office and Excel

## **Experience**

Bartender

Aug 2018 - Jan 2021

Ground Round - Grand Forks, ND

- Spoke to customers and recommended specials to build rapport, retention, and customer loyalty.
- Managed carry-out and curbside pickup orders.
- Recommended house specials to new customers to boost revenue.
- Poured draft beers, wine selections, and non-alcoholic beverages to fulfill dining room and bar orders.
- Monitored open bar tabs, closed out bills for departing customers, and processed cash and credit transactions.

Customer Service Specialist

Aug 2017 - Apr 2018

Best Buy - Grand Forks, ND

- Provided solutions, recommendations, and replacements, using an empathetic approach and demeanor.
- · Checked statuses of online orders, and service requests through the fulfillment software
- Completed paperwork associated with merchandise, price adjustments, customer returns, and cash register operation.
- Collected cash drawers at the end of each shift, making sure each till was balanced
- Used selling techniques to sell the store credit card

Bartender Shift Manager

Aug 2014 - Aug 2017

St. Patrick's Resturaunt - New Prague, MN

- Helped food and bar drinks come out in a quick and orderly fashion
- Conducted monthly inventories to assure an adequate supply of liquor, ice, glasses, and other necessities.

- Managed stocking of bar, making sure everything was prepped and ready for the next shift.
- Balanced the till, and pull tab money at the end of each shift.
- Completed all closing shift side work and closed the restaurant down.

## **Education**

Northland Community and Technical College - East Grand Forks, ND Currently studying at Northland Community and Technical College for an Associates in Business degree. Expected to graduate in the spring of 2021. Expect to pursue a bachelor's degree in this area of study.